grandoldteam.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy policy | GrandOldTeam

We are GrandOldTeam ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please [contact us](https://www.grandoldteam.com/contact/).

## What information we hold about you

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

  * Your name or username.
  * Your email address.
  * Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

## How your personal information is used

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

## Other ways we may use your personal information.

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

## Keeping your data secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

## Cookie policy

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on this page.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please [contact us](https://www.grandoldteam.com/contact/). If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may [contact us](https://www.grandoldteam.com/contact/) to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please [contact us](https://www.grandoldteam.com/contact/) if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Editorial Policy

While we welcome all forms of contribution, we appreciate well-structured, informative, and interestingly written pieces dealing exclusively with Everton. The decision to publish, and the degree of editorial control exercised by GrandOldTeam.com, will be at our discretion. However, we do request that you read and abide by our Terms and Conditions of Use. GrandOldTeam assumes an open-door policy with regard to submissions and contributions. This website is provided by fans for the fans which means that we provide a forum for you to air your views, whether we agree with them or not. We always welcome reader responses that challenge any viewpoints espoused in the articles we publish and often we will counter such pieces with arguments of our own. Our line-up of columnists and contrbutors aims to provide a wide spectrum of viewpoints but, as is of often the case, it is critical content that gets seized upon as evidence of perceived or inherent bias. Please note: Just because we publish an article does not necessarily mean we agree with the views of the author. All materials published on GrandOldTeam may be subject to editorial review. This usually comprises minor text editing and formatting for web layout, page presentation, and readability. Spelling, grammar, and other errors may be corrected during this process. Content will rarely be changed as part of the editorial process, unless the meaning is unclear or obscure, statements made expose us to liability, or where the content is either abusive or similarly deemed unacceptable conduct. We may add links to other websites or to other pages on GrandOldTeam, as we deem appropriate. 

## Advertising

This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.  
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the users interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

#### DoubleClick for Publishers (Google Inc.)

DoubleClick for Publishers is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. that allows the Owner to run advertising campaigns in conjunction with external advertising networks that the Owner, unless otherwise specified in this document, has no direct relationship with. In order to opt out from being tracked by various advertising networks, Users may make use of [Youronlinechoices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). In order to understand Google's use of data, consult [Google's partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).  
This service uses the "Doubleclick" Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

#### Criteo (Criteo SA)

Criteo is an advertising service provided by Criteo SA.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: France – [Privacy Policy](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.criteo.com/deactivate-criteo-banners/).

#### AppNexus (AppNexus Inc.)

AppNexus is an advertising service provided by AppNexus Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices).

#### RhythmOne (Burst Media Corporation)

RhythmOne is an advertising service provided by RhythmOne, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://www.rhythmone.com/opt-out). 

#### Rubicon Project (The Rubicon Project, Inc.)

Rubicon Project is an advertising service provided by The Rubicon Project, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/).

#### Index Exchange (Index Exchange)

Index Exchange is an advertising service provided by Index Exchange.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

#### Sovrn (Sovrn Holdings, Inc)

Sovrn is an advertising service provided by Sovrn Holdings, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/) – [Opt Out](https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/2672?v=1&nt=0&nw=false).

#### bRealTime (EMX Digital LLC)

bRealTime is an advertising service provided by EMX Digital LLC (a subsidiary of Engine Media LLC).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.brealtime.com/privacy-policy/) – [Opt Out](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/).

#### District M (District M, Inc.)

District M is an advertising service provided by District M, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://districtm.net/en/page/data-and-privacy-policy/) – [Opt Out](https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html).

#### 152 Media (152 Media, LLC.)

152 Media is an advertising service provided by 152 Media, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.152media.com/privacy.html) – [Opt Out](https://app.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/8a17cf9b-19c4-4f99-a32d-4dd3b0f21c93).

#### Ad You Like (Ad You Like.)

Ad You Like is an advertising service provided by Ad You Like

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.adyoulike.com/privacy_policy.php) – Opt Out.

#### Google AdSense (Google Inc.)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the "Doubleclick" Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.
